Aha made absolute fools of us all.
The curse of Elation still has me
pinned firmly to this chessboard.
Pre-dating the birth of Aeons and the era of the primordial nouspores,
leviathans were already entrenched at the absolute beginning.
Seems like everything's in place.
At this moment, "Preservation" and "Imagenesis" have finally merged into a single theme.
What is the most surefire way
to destroy an unfinished painting once and for all?
I did it. All of it.
The masses revere these monstrosities as heroes,
place their faith in them, worship them...
I come to appraise.
I come to analyze.
Haven't had such a hearty meal in a long time.
I come to render.
...Brings back memories.
I weave the cosmos into brocade.
Breathe soul into painted stones,
let the jewels of heaven rise as they will.
Hear that?
The referee is in place,
and it's time for the Supplicants to make their entrance.
All eyes across the cosmos will be fixed on
Ahatopia to witness this god-slaying game.
And today, we set sail once more!
To deceive! To bait!
To slay! The awakened... Oroboros!
Please enjoy
this end-of-the-century magic trick, co-starring gods and mortals alike!